Ah!
(Howard:)Okay, I have now officially moved out
of my mother's house.
(Howard:)You are now the only woman in my life
who I'll see naked in the bathroom.
(Bernadette:)I know this wasn't easy. You doing okay?
Well, I'm fine. It's just her I'm worried about.
(Bernadette:)- She'll be okay. She's a grown woman.
- I know.
(Howard:)It's just ever since my dad left,
I've felt responsible for her.
(Bernadette:)That's a lot for a kid to deal with.
(Howard:)She was just so sad all the time.
(Howard:)I was the only person
who could cheer her up.
(Howard:)Well, me and Ben and Jerry.
(Bernadette:)She's lucky you were there.
(Howard:)You know, she's why I first got into magic.
(Howard:)I would do little shows for her.
(Howard:)Hang up a bedsheet like it was a curtain,
put on a top hat and cape.
And partway through the act, I would say
I needed a volunteer from the audience...